{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
有鹿er\h\h\hoY_Yo
汤包小螺螺\h\h\h天天开心鸭
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
麦奇麦奇\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
Netflix1207
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
三层楼的女孩
库珀
Cooper!
居然把房间刷成粉色
Who paints a room pink?
等等  等等
Wait, wait...
别这样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
你会把事情搞砸的
You're the one that's gonna have to shit that out later.
轻轻松松
Piece of cake.
天哪
Jesus Christ!
门铃需要修理一下了
Doorbell needs fixing.
喝一杯吗
Bourbon?
你为什么要搬到郊区来
What brings you out to the suburbs?
环境变了
Change of scenery.
我和我的妻子马上要生孩子了
Uh, my wife and I got a baby on the way,
这家伙又需要一个院子
and this guy needed a yard.
就想着找个大点的地方
Thought a little bit of elbow room
对所有人都有好处
would do everybody some good.
家庭不错
Family's good.
有泥地也不错
Dirt's good.
没在泥地里打过滚的
Kids can't grow up right without some mud on their jeans
口袋里没装过青蛙的孩子都长不大
and a frog in their pocket.
你呢  你住在附近吗
What about you? Do you live around here?
84年的时候就住这了
Since '84,
久到足够见证所有事情
long enough to see my fair share of things
周而复始
come and go.
所以你是修女
So you're a nun...?
上帝啊
Good Lord.
我记得芝加哥人思想没那么落后
I remember Chicago being more progressive than that.
我们是新教徒
No, we're Protestant.
我是牧师
I'm the pastor.
抱歉  我应该想到的
I apologize. I should've known.
我和我妻子都不是很虔诚的教徒
My wife and I aren't very religious.
-我只是  -没关系
- I just didn't-- Don't sweat it, slick.
在这里没这么拘束
We're more laidback out here.
我家大门常打开
And my door is always open,
开放怀抱等你
if you care to learn more.
宝宝
Hey, Bunny!
你好  猛男  新家第一晚感觉如何
Hi, Tiger. How was your first night?
还不错  给你看看这地方
Oh, great. Look at this place.
你刚睡醒吗
Did you just wake up?
小家伙怎么样了
Hey, how's the little kicker doing?
来和爸爸打个招呼
Say hi to Daddy.
你好  小南瓜头
Hey, little Pumpkin Head.
我的天  别把你女儿叫成
Oh my God, you're not calling your daughter
小南瓜头  行吗
"Pumpkin Head." Please.
怎么不行呢
Oh, come on, babe.
你看看你的肚子有多大
You've seen the size of your belly.
这是唯一的解释
That's the only explanation.
你今天有什么安排
So, what's on the agenda today?
打算做些什么
How's the schedule looking?
今天的安排没有太多
Oh, the schedule feels great.
收拾一下这间房
I will finish this room
挂了电话就开干
as soon as I'm off the phone with you
下午转战厨房
and I'll move on to the kitchen in the afternoon.
装饰一下  打磨一下吗
So what, like painting, sanding,
把墙上的洞凿开
opening that giant gaping hole?
你确定不用我帮你
Ugh, are you sure you don't want me
打电话叫装修工吗  唐
to call in some pros, Don?
工程量浩大啊
This is a lot of work.
不用  不用叫任何人
No, we're not calling anybody.
我做得到
I got this.
我们的城堡若假以他人之手建成
How could I sleep at night
夜里我岂能安然入睡
knowing some other jerkwad built your castle?
你能睡着是因为房顶不会漏水
Well, you'd sleep because the roof wouldn't leak.
那是什么
What's that?
这地方到处都是垃圾
Oh, there's piles of junk all over this place.
别想太多
Please don't be paranoid.
我相信你
I trust you.
糟糕  我该走了
Shit, I got to go.
我有  10点要开会
I've got, um, team's proposals at ten.
晚上给你打电话
Anyway, I'll call you tonight, okay?
爱你
Love you.
再见
Bye.
所以一旦你得知干墙的尺寸
"So once you get your drywall size,
你需要做的就是亲自检查
you want to just check by hand
看看哪里需要修补
and see where does the drywall give in?
幸运的是  现在只有一小部分
Now, luckily, it's only a small section--"
♪ 迷失在 ♪
♪ So lost in darkness ♪
♪ 自私的黑暗中 ♪
♪ In and out of selfishness ♪
♪ 积我所有的梦想 ♪
♪ Hoarding all my dreams ♪
♪ 别无他法 ♪
♪ Was just no way to be ♪
♪ 请你赠予我珍贵之物 ♪
♪ Then you gifted me such a precious thing ♪
♪ 成为当之无愧的爱人的机会 ♪
♪ A chance to be someone who deserved love ♪
♪ 当我听见 ♪
♪ When I heard ♪
♪ 一滴眼泪 ♪
♪ A single tear ♪
正好合适
Close enough.
♪ 我看到 ♪
♪ It showed me what ♪
♪ 一滴眼泪 ♪
♪ A single tear ♪
♪ 真正的力量可能是 ♪
♪ Real strength could be ♪
♪ 一滴眼泪 ♪
♪ A single tear ♪
♪ 当一滴眼泪落下
♪ As a single teardrop fell ♪
怎么回事
What the hell?
什么鬼玩意儿钻头  操
Oh, piece of shit drill, motherfucker!
哎我天
Oh, God!
最近怎样  科赫先生
How's it going, Mr. Koch?
换换生活方式  对吗
Change of pace, huh?
差不多吧
Something like that.
像你这样的人打算一直在这生活吗
How's a guy like you planning to survive out here?
我会解决的
I'll figure it out.
无法想象这可怜的夜生活
Can't imagine there's much of a nightlife.
没有撩人眼球的夜总会
No fancy supper clubs.
没有脱衣舞女来吸引顾客
No strippers to woo clients with.
有很多脱衣舞女
Uh, there's plenty of strippers.
只是没有顾客需要吸引
It just don't have any clients left to woo.
说得对
True.
那么问题来了
Which begs the question,
你怎么能买得起这个地方
how exactly can you afford this place?
善良的丽兹
Good old Liz.
没错  我喜欢她
Yeah. I like her.
聪明的女人
Smart woman.
她会如何适应这种改变
How's she accepting this change?
她会继续开她的公司
She will keep her company running
孩子出生之后她就上班
and she'll commute once the baby's born.
这不代表我们的生活完蛋了
You know, it's not like our life's over.
只是
It's just...
更加成熟了
...it's maturing.
最好是这样  唐
It'd better be, Don.
联邦调查局拯救你于水深火热之中
Feds cut you one hell of a sweetheart deal,
fed  美国联邦政府工作人员
考虑很周全
all things considered.
要是你再搞砸一次就太丢人了
Be a shame if you fucked it all up again.
就这些吗
That it?
对
Yeah.
这是最后的文件
That's the last of it.
那座教堂很漂亮
That's a beautiful church.
什么鬼
Oh, shit!
厄洛斯进口
巴黎制造
你还好吧
You gonna be okay?
别在屋子里大便
Don't shit in the house.
该死的吃球机器
Goddamn machine likes to eat balls.
饿吗  渴吗
You hungry or thirsty?
又饿又渴吗
Both.
我可以给你来点鸡尾酒
Cocktails I have some control over.
吃的你击中了才有
Food can be hit or miss.
那就先来杯喝的吧
Well let's start with a drink, then.
聪明的男人
Smart man.
还不错
It's not bad.
我决定让你代言我的下一条广告
I'll quote you in the next ad.
你是来旅游还是迷路了
So, uh, are you visiting or lost?
我住这儿
Resident.
我在索尔和舍克那儿买了房子
I, uh, just bought the house on Saul and Circle.
怎么了
What?
你是同性恋吗
You queer?
你说什么
Excuse me?
不难回答吧
It's a simple question.
我快有小孩了
Yeah, I'm about to have a kid.
你问的是什么问题
What kind of a question is that?
很简单  唐
Easy, Don.
同性恋也可以有孩子
Gay people can have kids, too.
没什么不对
Nothing wrong with that.
我知道  我
I know that. I--
我的婚姻很幸福
I'm happily married.
当然  你确实是
Of course, you are.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
对直男来说那个房子不太好
That house just seems to be bad news for straight men.
不过  你会没事的
Uh, but, uh, I'm sure you'll be fine.
再来一杯
How about a shot?
我欢迎新邻居的方式
You've got a real fucked up way of welcoming people
糟糕透了  吉利
to the neighborhood, Geary.
库珀
Cooper!
Cooper?
他娘的
Shit!
你吓死我了
You really suck, you know that?
克莱奥和杰森
You know, Cleo and Jason
又提出了海德公园项目
brought up the Hyde Park Project again.
太扫兴了
So frustrating
还要再拒绝他们一次
to keep having to telling them no.
你知道我还讨厌什么吗
You know what I also hate?
总是想尿尿
Having to pee all the time.
天呐  肚子再大一点
God, if these things get any more swollen
我就站不直了
I won't be able to stand up straight.
你那里进展如何
So, how is it going over there?
还行  我今天干了不少活
Great. I got a ton done today.
未来一片光明
I'm feeling positive about it.
太棒了  亲爱的
That's wonderful, babe.
厨房怎么样了
How's the kitchen shaping up?
其实我还没开始
Well, I actually didn't make it
收拾厨房
into the kitchen today,
不过厨房是明天的头等大事
but it is the first thing on tomorrow's list.
你确定不需要
Are you sure you don't need some
别人帮忙  亲爱的
extra hands, babe?
我确定  宝宝
I'm sure, Bunny.
一切进展顺利
Everything's going fine.
别忘了麦洛周末要来
Don't forget Milo's coming up this weekend.
如果你想帮忙
But if you wanna help,
现在你可以帮我做点事
you can do me a favor right now.
做什么
What's that?
把电话放低一点
Just tilt that phone down to those
给我看看你诱人的胸
beautiful boobs one more time.
等你收拾完厨房给你看完整的
That's all you get until I see a finished kitchen.
好了  晚安
All right. Good night.
你好  爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
我真是太皮太皮了
I've been such a naughty, naughty girl.
只有你有办法降服我
You always know exactly how to treat me.
我会听你的话  爸爸
Oh, I'll do whatever you say, Daddy.
你会惩罚我吗
Are you gonna punish me?
你好  爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
我真是太不听话了
I've been such a naughty, naughty girl.
等等  出去
Hey, hey, out!
你看起来真狼狈
That looks terrific.
老旧管道
Old pipes.
看起来没那么老
They don't look so old.
有什么可以帮你的吗
Can I help you with something?
我只是很喜欢这里
I just like it here.
-什么  -这房子
- What? - The house.
这里通常都没人
It's usually empty.
好吧  这里被我买了
Oh, well, I bought it.
所以不会再没人了
So it's not empty anymore.
可惜了
Hmm, shame.
我该进去了
Uh, I'd better get back inside.
好  没问题
Sure. No problem.
回头见
See you around.
♪ 淬炼 ♪
♪ Distill ♪
♪ 千锤百炼 ♪
♪ Break them all down ♪
♪ 淬炼 ♪
♪ Distill ♪
♪ 分裂瓦解 ♪
♪ Tear them all apart ♪
♪ 淬炼 ♪
♪ Distill ♪
操
Fuck!
见鬼
Oh, Christ.
还能抽吗  老爹
Still smoke, Dad?
然后这里  我们要把墙纸
And in here, we will change this wallpaper
换成没那么丑的
to something a lot less hideous.
我们是谁
Who's "we?"
我老婆和我
My wife and I.
确定吗  这个挺复古的
Are you sure? It's very retro.
你说不定会后悔
You might end up regretting it.
好  如果我们辗转反侧了  我就通知你
Uh, well, I'll let you know if we lose any sleep over it.
一个从不自我怀疑的男人  是吧
A man who never second-guesses himself, huh?
这是什么
What's this?
这个
Now, this...
这才叫复古
This is retro.
小壁橱吗
A tiny closet?
告诉我你们会保留这个
Please tell me you guys are keeping this.
我就是为此才买下这房子的
Entire reason I bought the house.
有品位
You have great taste.
这里面有什么
What's in here?
-白色吗  -被你发现了
- White? - Oh, you got me.
我老婆选的
The wife picked it out.
好像是叫法式香草白
I think it was called "French Vanilla"
或是别的类似的名字
or something like that.
听说是明年的热门颜色
It's supposed to be next year's trendy color.
还有别的想展示给我看的吗
Anything else you wanna show me?
能帮个忙吗
Can you do me a favor?
什么忙
What's that?
掐我脖子
Choke me.
这裙子在地板上的时候更美
This dress looked better on the floor.
刚才比我想象中还好
That was even better than I hoped for.
别用那种眼神看我
Oh, don't look at me like that.
这是我应得的
I earned that.
太夸张了
That is insane!
我知道  来  看这个
I know. Well, check this out.
这他妈是什么
What the hell is that?
不知道  看台吗
I don't know. Bleachers?
也许他们听说了我们火热的性生活
Hey, maybe they heard about how hot our sex life is
所以安装了观众席
and had them installed, huh?
我的天
Oh, my God.
我只是不明白评估时
I just don't understand how you missed this
你怎么会忽略了这个
during the appraisal.
你当时也在场  并没有这些东西
You were here too, and these weren't.
我去给地产中介打电话
I'm gonna call the real estate agent.
为什么
Why?
她能做什么  这些已经在这了
What is she going to do? They're here.
因为我不想要这些东西
Because I want them gone.
屋顶维修费时费钱
The ceiling repair is gonna cost time and money
-我们应该去要补偿  -宝宝
- and we should be compensated.- Bunny...
宝宝  放轻松好吗  修起来很简单的
Bunny, relax, okay? This is an easy fix.
可能只是个劣质的补片
It's probably just a shoddy patch, all right?
结构上没有受损
No structural damage.
我和麦洛能解决的  小意思
Me and Milo can tackle this, no problem.
相信我  好吗
Trust me, okay?
我相信你  宝贝
I trust you, babe.
我只是想你
I just don't want you to bite off
量力而为
more than you can chew.
我应该用个大铁桶的
Eh, I should have got a dumpster.
在干嘛呢
What you doing?
你知道我的
You know me,
努力干活  奋发图强
I'm just working hard, cranking away.
听起来很有趣
Sounds fun.
需要帮忙吗
Want some help?
不了
Nah.
正在干些力气活
Doing a bunch of heavy lifting in here.
我自己就行
I got this.
行吧
Okay.
听着  昨晚很刺激
Look, last night was super-hot,
但我们不该这样
but we shouldn't.
在我老婆孩子来之前
You know, I got to get this place tip-top
我得把这地方收拾好
before the wife and baby get here,
但我还有
and there's still, like,
很多事没做完
a laundry list of things to do.
你说得对  但那是之后的事
True, but that's later.
现在呢
What about right now?
我不能  你应该理解的
I can't. I'm sure you understand.
好吧
Sure.
我理解
I understand.
你好啊  猛男
Hey, Tiger.
天哪
Jesus...
什么鬼东西
What the fuck?
礼拜六了  蠢货
It's Saturday, idiot.
门铃不错
Nice doorbell.
好吧  确实有点惊悚
Well, that's certainly creepy.
这只是冰山一角
You don't know the half of it.
你们这种变态是为此买单呢还是
Did you freaks pay extra for that feature or...
闭嘴  混蛋
Shut up, dick.
我们不知情
We didn't know this was there.
好吧  我不懂
Well, I don't know, man.
把阁楼修成客房
Turn the attic into a guest room.
在爱彼迎上租出去  为观看收取高额费用
Airbnb it, charge a fortune to watch.
如果这周内不修好
This is gone by the weekend
老婆就不来了
or there's not gonna be a wife left to watch.
好吧  为了你的孩子
Well, for the sake of your kid,
我们最好开始干活了
we better get to work.
你的工具在哪
Where are your tools?
就在那里
Right there.
就这个
That's it?
你准备用一把瑞士军刀
You plan on renovating an entire house
来翻修整栋住宅吗
with a Swiss army knife?
怎么  不够吗
What? Is that not enough?
不够
No.
抬一下
Lift.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- You good? - Yeah.
好了  开始吧
All right. Here we go.
公司怎么样了
How's the firm anyway?
不怎么样
Shit.
新条例简直挡住了我们的财路
New regulations got us by the balls.
你退出得很及时
You got out at the right time.
虽然不太得体  但是  你知道的
Maybe not gracefully, but, you know?
你至少还在赚钱吧
You still making money, at least?
没以前多
Not as much.
同样的报酬却需要加倍的工作
Have to work twice as hard for it.
我也想找一个丽兹
Need to find a Liz for myself.
如果你怕干活
It's a bad idea if you, uh,
那这就是个坏主意
are afraid of hard work.
王八蛋  难道你没看到这块超重的石膏板
Motherfucker, you don't see me holding the other side
正有一半被我举在头顶吗
of this heavy-ass drywall above my head?
而且还是免费的
Free of charge, I might add?
听着  我替你赚了那么多钱
Hey, listen, all the money I've made you,
才几个小时的无偿服务并不过分
couple hours of gratis isn't too much to ask.
好吧 你的房子确实挺好的
Well, you do have a pretty nice house.
接下来干什么  安珀比餐吧
What's next? Applebee's?
这就是你老婆吗
Is that the wife?
你的意思是  这谦虚的混蛋没跟你说过吗
You mean this modest motherfucker didn't tell you?
他基本上掌控了整个芝加哥
He basically ran Chicago.
国王唐  我们是这么称呼他的
King Don, we called him.
我确实成功过
I had a good run.
你是用顶层公寓换了那个妓院吗
You traded a penthouse for a whorehouse?
那你就正式成为城里最疯狂的人了
That might officially make you the craziest man in town.
等等  怎么回事
Wait, what?
他没跟你说过吗
Oh, he didn't tell you?
国王唐现在是
King Don is the proud owner
波兹密斯前妓院自豪的主人了
of Portsmith's former house of ill repute.
那是一百多年前的事了
That was over a hundred years ago.
好吧  怪不得
Well, might explain some things, though.
说到享乐
Speaking of pleasure,
这里的选择不太多  对吧
a little light on options in here, isn't it?
搬到郊区的人  要么是为了成家
You move to the suburbs to start a family,
要么就是所有人都觉得你是个王八蛋
or because everyone thinks you're an asshole.
对  因为你就是个王八蛋
Right. Because you're an asshole.
这附近肯定有大学吧
Certainly there's a college around here, right?
我之前看到一两个可爱的姑娘走在路上
Like, I saw one or two cute girls walking around earlier.
没有大学
No college.
但是  格温·马丁等下会来
But, uh, Gwen Martin will be in later.
格温·马丁是谁
Who's Gwen Martin?
她开了个情色陶艺班
She runs an erotic pottery class.
但她是个女权主义者
She's a feminist, though.
非常好
That's great.
我就是女权主义者
I'm a feminist.
我也是  小伙子
Me too, son.
你要保证不会跟丽兹说
Promise me you won't say a word to Liz
任何关于昨晚的事
about last night.
我跟她发过誓不喝酒的
I swore to her I wouldn't drink.
兄弟法则啊  老铁
Bro code, bro!
好兄弟
Good man.
我头疼死了  我要喝咖啡
My head's killing me. I need coffee.
你要来一杯吗
You want some?
你的助理已经做了一壶了
Your assistant already brewed a pot.
早上好  唐
Morning, Don.
你他妈怎么在这里
What the hell are you doing here?
只是顺路
I stopped by.
麦洛让我进来的  怎么了
Milo let me in. What's wrong?
什么怎么了  你在搞笑吗
"What's wrong?" Are you kidding me?
好吧  让我们把事情理清楚
All right. Let's get something straight.
这是我的人生
This is my life...
萨拉  我叫萨拉
Sarah. My name is Sarah.
好  萨拉
Great, Sarah.
听着  我不是在瞎胡闹
Look, I'm not fucking around right now.
别误会  那一晚很开心
It was a fun night, don't get me wrong,
但我再也不想看到你出现在我家里了
but I don't ever wanna see you here in my house ever again.
你明白我的意思吗
You understand me?
当然了  老兄
Sure, man.
别大惊小怪的
Don't make it weird.
这里一切都好吧
All good in here?
刚才他妈的是怎么回事
What the fuck was that?
没事  没事
Nothing. Nothing.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
得了吧  唐  别忽悠我了
Come on, don't bullshit me, Don.
你到底干啥了
What did you do?
我啥也没干  好吧
I didn't do anything, okay?
你想多了
You're overreacting.
你站在那儿  威胁女人
You're standing there threatening a woman
你还说我想多了
and I'm overreacting?
好吧  听着
All right. Look,
我犯错了  千万别告诉别人  好吗
between you and me, I fucked up, all right?
但不是我主动找的
I didn't go looking for it.
也不是我要求的  我甚至压根没想这样
I didn't ask for it, I didn't even really want it.
事情就那么发生了  她今天又来
It just happened, she came back.
我告诉她之前是不对的
I explained to her it was a mistake.
不会有问题的
It's not gonna be a problem.
咱们现在能赶紧去五金店买
Can we just go to the hardware store for...
你到底要再错多少次
How many times are you gonna fuck up
才能觉悟呢
until you get a clue?
丽兹怀孕了  怀的是你的孩子
Liz is pregnant. That's your blood.
她拼命帮你赚钱持家的时候
And you're out here trying to recapture your glory days
你竟然还幻想着重振当年的雄风  是吗
while she's busting ass to keep a roof over your head?
丽兹是我朋友  老兄
She's my friend, dude.
你  你让我怎么面对她
What-- How am I supposed to look her in the eye now?
丽兹不需要知道这些  好吗
Liz doesn't need to find out, okay?
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be fine.
你什么时候才能学会为别人着想
When are you gonna start thinking about someone
而不是这么自私
other than yourself?
该死的  事情就是这样了  麦洛
Oh, fuck, it is what it is, Milo, okay?
如果你看不下去
If you can't handle it,
趁我回来前赶紧走人
don't be here when I come back!
库珀
Cooper!
确实亮不起来
Of course not.
喜欢我的小把戏吗
You like my trick?
萨拉  你疯了么  我差点伤到你
Sarah, are you crazy? I almost fucked you up.
跟你闹着玩呢
I'm just playing.
听着  唐的所作所为  我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry Don's such an asshole
但你必须离开
but you need to get out of here.
这就没意思了
Well, that's no fun.
你想帮我  还是想怎么样
You wanna help me or what?
麦洛
Milo?
好了  混蛋  快出来吧
All right, dick, you can come out now.
哈哈
还没
真高兴周末
你能来帮忙
听着  我很抱歉和你发脾气
请相信我能把事情解决好
已经开始认识
邻居了吗
哈哈
还没
真高兴周末
你能来帮忙
听着  我很抱歉和你发脾气
请相信我能把事情解决好
已经开始认识
邻居了吗
没事了
麦洛 Stone
宝宝  这周末真是要我老命了
Oh, it's been a killer weekend, Bun.
我们干了很多活儿
We got a ton done.
麦洛开心吗
Did Milo have fun
还是说你把他往死里用
or did you just work him to death?
是他自己非要往死里干
He wanted to work the whole time.
来看这里
Check this out.
猛男  我真是被你惊到了
I'm seriously impressed, Tiger.
和你说了  不用担心
I told you not to worry.
等等  那是什么
Wait, what was that?
怎么了
What?
我刚看到你身后有什么东西
I just saw something behind you.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
唐  别蒙我  麦洛还在屋里吗
Don, don't mess with me, is Milo still there?
不在
No.
他得赶回去上班
He had to head back to work.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我也说不好
I don't know.
我感觉刚才看到有个人  我有点害怕了
I thought I saw someone. Now I'm getting freaked out.
反正又不是你今晚
Well, you're not the one who has to
要睡在这里  宝宝
sleep here tonight, Bunny.
看看这边
Check all this out.
亲爱的  看起来真不错
It looks great, babe.
亲爱的  如果真有人在这儿
Babe, if somebody else was in here,
库珀早就叫起来了
Cooper would be all crazy right now.
那倒是
Good point.
你是想让我睡觉时
You want I should sleep with a hammer
在枕头下放把锤子  以防万一吗
under my pillow tonight, just in case?
最好这样
You probably better.
我可不想过去时看到你出什么意外
I don't want to have to kill someone when I get there.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事  没事
Yeah. Yeah.
我就是有些累了  宝宝
I'm just getting tired, babe.
快歇息吧  亲爱的
Well, rest up, okay, babe?
我明天再打给你
I'll call you tomorrow.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
进展如何啊  唐
How's it going, Don?
你想说说吗
You wanna talk about it?
没啥好说的
Nothing to talk about.
那就从你的房子说起吧
Let's start with the house.
她感觉怎么样
How is she coming along?
还行吧
Just fine.
还行  是吗
Fine, huh?
你知道  当女人到了一定年纪以后
You know, when a woman gets to be a certain age,
往往希望事情变得简单些
she doesn't like to be futzed with too much.
房子的事儿也一样  我想
Houses aren't that different, I guess.
事情
It's...
事情是有些麻烦
It's been hard.
我信
I bet.
这房子很麻烦的
This house is a bitch.
什么意思
What's that mean?
一些地方有它特别的属性
Well, just that certain places have personalities,
有的地方很腐旧
and sometimes they're rotten.
重新翻修一新确实要费些功夫
It takes a real strong hand to turn them around again.
我在努力
I'm trying.
承受住考验的人
"Blessed is the man who remains
最终会得到幸福的
steadfast under trial."
帅哥  你好啊
Hi, handsome.
小库
Coop?
库珀
Cooper?
-萨拉吗  -没错  萨拉
- Sarah? - Sarah, yeah.
没有姓吗
No last name?
她肯定有姓
I imagine she has one
可我又没查过他身份证  好吗
but I didn't check her ID, okay?
她就住这个小区
She lives in the neighborhood,
她总是不停来骚扰我
she won't stop fucking with me!
看这个
Look.
然后呢
And?
然后
And?!
你刚也看到我的狗了
You see the dog, right?
难道你认为是它自己跳进
You think he jumped into the
那该死的烘干机里吗
goddamn dryer by himself?
难道它自己把烘干机打开的吗
Did he turn it on, too?
拜托  哥们  是她干的
Come on, man. It was her.
麦洛
Milo!
赶紧给我回电话
Call me back.
听着  我把嫌疑人姓名和案件情况
Look, I'll put the name and the description
都写在报告里了
in my report.
但没有丝毫强行进入的迹象
But there's no signs of forced entry,
也没有挣扎的痕迹
no evidence of a struggle,
而且是你一直睡在楼上
and you were sleeping upstairs the whole time
你还什么都没听到
and didn't hear a thing.
好吧
Oh, great.
那我谢谢你了
Well, thank you for your service.
这就是你的执法理念吗
Is this your idea of law enforcement?
你就探个头  耸个肩
You just poke your head and you shrug your shoulders
像个白痴一样
like a dipshit.
你什么忙都没帮上
You didn't do anything.
如还有异常  随时联系我们
Please let us know if anything else comes up...
国王唐
King Don.
我讨厌你把这地方弄得一团糟
I hate what you've done with the place.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉什么
For what?
我很抱歉从一开始就不诚实
I'm sorry for not being honest from the start.
我很抱歉不公平地对待你
I'm sorry for treating you unfairly.
我很抱歉让你觉得自己无足轻重
I'm sorry for making you feel unimportant.
总重要的  我很抱歉威胁了你
And most of all, I'm sorry for threatening you.
你这是早就编好的吗
Did you rehearse that?
我应该那样  但不是的
I deserved that, but no.
真的  我很抱歉
I mean it, I'm sorry.
我明白你为何这么气愤
I understand why you feel so angry.
你这样对待他人
Well, it's not a very nice way
可不太友善  唐
to treat someone, Don.
我希望你能对你的妻子和孩子好一点
I hope you treat your wife and kid better than this.
我爱我的妻子
I love my wife.
多希望之前我能再坚强些
And I wish I was stronger.
我为你备了点东西作为补偿
To make all this up to you, I got you something.
有妇之夫的礼物吗
A gift from a married man.
听起来很像在贿赂我
Sounds a lot like a bribe.
你想要的话  就去厨房拿
If you're interested, it's in the kitchen.
我接受你的道歉  唐
I appreciate the apology, Don.
我不想事情变得更糟
I don't want things to get any uglier.
你好  宝宝
Hey, Bunny.
干什么呢  猛男
Hey, Tiger? What you doin'?
干活呢
Just working.
麦洛给我发了条信息
So, I got a text from Milo.
他说什么
Oh, yeah?
挺奇怪的  他说我们得谈谈
It was kind of weird. He said we needed to talk.
你知道是怎么回事吗
Any idea why?
一点不知道  宝宝
No, I have no clue, babe.
唐  有事千万别瞒我
Don, just be honest with me.
是装修碰到什么麻烦了吗
Look, is the renovation in trouble?
进展还顺利吗
Is that what it is?
是他看到了什么事
Did he see some things that he thinks
需要告诉我吗
I should know about?
根本没有
No!
猛男  冷静
Tiger, calm down.
丽兹  一切都很好  好吧
Everything is fine, Liz! All right?
你要把这个砸我脸上吗
Are you gonna throw this in my face now?!
我压根不知道麦洛为何联系你
I have no idea why Milo called you,
但无论如何  请你打给他  搞清楚
but please, by all means, call him, find out.
我现在很忙  我得接着干活了
I'm busy. I-- I wanna get back to work.
操
Shit!
萨拉
Sarah!
什么鬼
What the fuck!
天哪
Oh God!
已转到波兹密斯警察局
"You've reached the voicemail of Officer Henry Baker
亨利·贝克警官的语音信箱
of the Portsmith Police Department.
听到提示音后  请说出你的姓名
Please state your name, number, and detailed message
韦弗 警官
电话号码和详细的信息
at the sound of the tone.
一条照片信息
麦洛
要为自己做的
负责
求你了  放过我吧
Please stop!
为什么
Why?
为什么这样对我
Why are you doing this to me?
离我远点
Stay away from me!
有人吗
Hello?
猛男
Tiger?
库珀  过来呀
Cooper, come here, boy.
有人在吗
Hello?
库珀  来咯
Cooper, come here.
绝对不要这样的
Absolutely not.
天啊  唐  你怎么也不罩个床罩
Oh, Jesus, Don, no dropcloth?
唐  你这是洒的啥呀
What did you spill, Don. What did you spill here?
唐  你这是在干啥呢
What are you doing, Don?
老天啊
Oh my God.
波兹密斯郡日报
1909年8月2日  星期一
警方突袭当地妓院
女孩尸体未找到
拜托  唐纳德
Come on, Donald.
你这是闹哪样
What are you up to?
妈呀
Jesus!
我非常非常抱歉
I'm so, so, so sorry.
不好意思  有什么需要我帮你的吗
I'm sorry, can I help you?
我不是有意要吓到你的
I didn't mean to frighten you.
我叫萨拉
My name is Sarah.
我一直在帮助唐
I've been helping Don.
帮助唐？
Helping Don?
不好意思  你这是什么意思
I'm sorry, what does, what does that mean exactly?
帮他为你准备好这个房子
You know, getting the house ready for you.
因为你是个木工吗
Because you're a carpenter?
不是的  女士  我就是个跑腿的
No, ma'am. More like a gofer.
需要干壁钉吗  老板  当然
"Drywall screws, boss? Sure thing!"
我是个建筑狂人  唐不会拒绝
I'm an architecture nut. Don couldn't say no.
对  这的确不是他的强项
No. That definitely isn't his strong suit.
有多久了
How long?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
你的宝宝
Your baby?
离她出生还有多久
How long till she's due?
十二周
Twelve weeks.
如果她像我一点  她就会准时出生
If she's anything like me, she'll be on time.
但如果她像爸爸  那就要迟到了
If she's like her father, much later.
我能摸一下吗
May I?
不太好吧
I don't think so.
有人来了
Someone's here.
科赫太太
Missus Koch?
怎么了
Yes?
我是艾丽·穆勒
I'm Ellie Mueller.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
我猜  你是水管工
Let me guess, you're the plumber?
我不是  亲爱的  我在街对面工作
No, darling, I work across the street.
不过我确实要处理很多人的破事
But I do deal with a lot of people's shit.
这样啊  唐没有提起过你  抱歉
That's right, Don did mention you, sorry.
你要进来吗
Would you like to come in?
不如我们在外面说吧
Why don't we chat outside instead?
好的  没问题  等我一下  好吗
Okay. Sure,give me a sec, okay?
很抱歉我有些失礼
Sorry to be rude but
人呢
Hello?
唐怎么样
So how's Don doing?
他看起来很累  但他很勤快
He looks tired, but he's a workhorse.
他现在在哪里
Where... where is he now?
我不太清楚
I'm not really sure.
他应该是去遛狗了
He must have just taken the dog for a run.
我应该先打个电话的  但我想给他个惊喜
I should have called first, but I wanted to surprise him.
你觉得这是个成功的婚姻吗
Would you say it's a good marriage?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
这个房子有些传言
This house has a history
它会唤醒人性的恶
of bringing out the worst in people.
我就是想确认一下你们两个准备好了
I just wanted make sure you two are prepared for that.
好的
Right.
这个的确需要做很多工作
It clearly needs a lot of work,
但是  也没那么困难
but it's... it's not that bad.
我确定我们能完成
I'm sure we'll manage.
你是不会知道的  直到你开始
You never really know until you start
拆掉一个地方
tearing a place up, though.
谢谢你的关心  真的
Thank you for your concern, really,
但是我和唐经历过更糟糕的事
but Don and I have been through much worse,
所以我们会没事的
so we'll be fine.
我一点也没有被这个房子吓到
I am not creeped out by this house one bit.
我能完全控制自己的情绪
I am in complete control of my emotions.
就像碧昂斯一样
Just like Beyonce.
我的天
Oh, Christ.
去他妈的
Fuck this.
你好
Hi.
我很担心
I'm worried.
我丈夫太糟糕了
My husband is a fuck-up.
你不是第一个女人这么说
You're not the first woman to say that
她的丈夫
about her husband.
没错
No.
我不是说他总把马桶座翻上去
I don't mean he leaves the toilet seat up.
他骗了他的客户们
He defrauded his clients
骗走了他们的退休金
out of their retirement funds.
他差点被判15年
He barely avoided fifteen years in a federal prison.
他背叛了我
He cheated on me
在我试着怀孕的时候
while I was trying to get pregnant,
然后他坚持说买这个房子
and then he insists that buying this house
是我们的第二次机会  所以
was our second chance, so,
那你为什么留下来
So why'd you stay?
其他选择似乎更糟糕
The alternatives seemed worse.
人生就是一系列抉择组成的
Life is a series of choices.
因和果
Cause and effect.
好像唐还没有领悟人生的运作方式
Sounds like Don hasn't learned that dynamic yet.
我很害怕
I'm just scared.
我害怕他又开始喝酒
I'm scared he's drinking again.
他现在可能已经喝醉了
He's probably drunk right now.
我觉得这个房子把他推到了边缘
I think this house just pushed him right over the edge.
这个房子有个测试男人的习惯
This house has a habit of testing men.
我遇到过一些住在这里的家庭
I've met families who have lived there
幸福了好几年
happily for years
还有其他没有把它变成家的人
and others who never make it a home.
这些区别的原因就在于
The difference seems to come down to the character
搬进来住的人们的性格和决心
and determination of the people moving in.
那我们完蛋了
We're screwed, then.
那你准备怎么做
So what's the plan?
我不知道  等他回家
I don't know. Wait for him to come home,
醒醒酒
sober up.
然后真诚地为我们的未来促膝长谈
And then have a long, honest talk about our future.
你是个勇敢的女人 丽兹
You're a brave woman, Liz.
你想听听我的意见吗
You want my advice?
带着你的丈夫和宝宝
Get your husband and your baby
离那个房子远远的
far away from that house.
抱歉  你哪位呀
Excuse me?
唐
Don?
老天
Jesus.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
这里到底发生了什么
What the fuck is going on here?
一个派对
A party.
我丈夫呢
Where is my husband?
可能在楼上
Upstairs, I think.
来杯鸡尾酒
Cocktail?
滚开
Fuck off.
唐
Don?
Don!
要不要一起
Joining?
不用了
No.
唐
Don?
演出已经开始了
The show's already started.
上楼去
Go upstairs.
唐
Don?!
Don!
停下
Stop!
演出已经结束了吗
Is the show over already?
这才是我的女孩
That's my girl.
那个男演员穿着戏服
The male performers wore costumes
因为老板觉得混合色情
because the owner felt the mix of erotic
和怪诞能够提升体验
and grotesque heightened the experience.
他是对的
He was right.
我们很受欢迎  钱如流水地进账
We were popular, and the money flowed in.
有些夜晚  我们工作到黎明
Some nights, we'd work until dawn.
我们忙到没办法关注每一个人
It was too busy to keep an eye on everyone.
甚至是无辜的人
Even the innocent ones.
以及没那么无辜的人
Even the not-so-innocent.
他跟她玩了数月然后把她杀了
He played with her for months and then killed her,
把她的尸体扔在火车轨道上
dumping her body at the train tracks,
世界继续运转
and the world moved on.
有些人是的
Some of the world did.
他杀了我  我的尸体从没离开这房子
When he killed me, my body never left the house.
我曾是个明星
I was a star,
每一个进了这个门的男人都爱我
loved by the men who came through our doors,
但是没人质疑我的消失
but not one of them questioned my disappearance.
所有男人爱的是你给他们的权利
All men really love is the power you give them.
唐
Don.
我的天  我的天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我没有把他们都弄到手
I couldn't get them all.
唐  宝贝
Don, baby?
你怎么了 发生了什么
What happened to you? What happened?
听着 听着
Hey, look, look.
我不知道这个房子里到底发生了什么
I don't know what the fuck is going on in this house,
但是我们必须赶紧离开这里
but we got to get out of here right now.
没那么简单的
It's not that easy.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
宝宝  我又搞砸了
Bunny, I fucked up again.
你在说什么  唐
What does that mean, Don?
我感觉自己很没用
I just-- I felt so small.
我只是想再男人一次
I just wanted to be the man one more time.
你明白的对吧  宝宝
You understand that don't you, Bunny?
不
No!
我不明白
I don't!
宝宝
Bunny!
我保证我会改的
I promise I can change.
我保证这会不一样  宝宝  看着我
I promise it'll be different. Bunny, look at me.
宝宝  你只要说你明白
Bunny, you just have to say that you understand
而且没关系
and that it's okay.
求你了
Please.
这不行
It's not okay!
我能改的  丽兹
I can change, Liz!
我为你感到自豪  丽兹
I'm proud of you, Liz!
我以为你没办法坚持到最后
Thought you weren't gonna make it there at the end.
你好啊  丽兹
Hey, Liz.
丽兹
Liz!
不
Nope!
你做的很好
You did good.
我会给你一些
I'd offer you some,
但这不是七十年代了
but it isn't the seventies anymore.
你早就知道
You knew?
是的
Yeah,
我观察这个房子  它也观察我的房子
I watch this house and it watches mine.
你为什么不提醒我们
Why the fuck didn't you warn us?
人生就是一系列的选择  丽兹
Life is a series of choices, Liz.
你不能说服别人去做正确的事
You can't talk someone into doing the right thing
或错误的事
or the wrong thing.
我没办法别人拦在这个房子外
I couldn't keep someone out of this house
就像那些屋子里的女孩
any more than those girls inside
把别人拦在我的门外
could keep someone out of mine.
需要列出选项  看看他们会选什么
Need to lay the options out and see what they choose.
一个测试
A test.
没错
Exactly.
这看起来像是个不公平的游戏
It seems like a pretty shitty game.
是的  孩子
It is, kiddo.
但是规则不是我定的
But I didn't make the rules.
六个月后
你好呀 我的小天使
Hello, my little angel.
你一点也不想睡觉  是吧
You don't wanna sleep at all, do you?
你小睡以后  我们就去公园
After your nap, we're gonna go to the park.
你想去吗
Would you like that?
我好爱你
I love you so much.
这才是我的女孩
That's my girl.